<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HappyHour</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="desp1"> \n\n  <b>Anxiety</b> is a feeling of uneasiness and worry, usually generalized and unfocused as an overreaction to a situation
        that is only subjectively seen as menacing.It is often accompanied by muscular tension,restlessness, fatigue and problems in concentration.\n\n
        Anxiety is closely related to fear, which is a response to a real or perceived immediate threat; anxiety involves the expectation of future threat.\n\n
        People facing anxiety may withdraw from situations which have provoked anxiety in the past.Anxiety is a feeling of uneasiness and worry, usually
        generalized and unfocused as an overreaction to a situation that is only subjectively seen as menacing. It is often accompanied by muscular
        tension,restlessness, fatigue and problems in concentration. Anxiety is closely related to fear, which is a response to a real or perceived
        immediate threat; anxiety involves the expectation of future threat. People facing anxiety may withdraw from situations which have provoked
        anxiety in the past.\n\nAnxiety is a feeling of uneasiness and worry, usually generalized and unfocused as an overreaction to a situation that is only subjectively seen as menacing. It is often accompanied by muscular tension, restlessness,fatigue and problems in concentration. \n\n
        Anxiety is closely related to fear, which is a response to a real or perceived immediate threat; anxiety involves the expectation of future threat.People facing anxiety may withdraw from situations which have provoked anxiety in the past.\n\n
\n\n
        <b>Causes</b>:\n\n
      Anxiety is not always related to an underlying condition. It may be caused by:\n\n
Stress that can result from work, school, personal relationship\n\n
Emotional trauma \n\n
Financial concerns\n\n
Stress caused by a chronic or serious medical condition\n\n
A major event or performance\n\n
Side effect of certain medications\n\n
Alcohol consumption, drugs such as cocaine\n\n
    </string>


    <string name="desplease" >  \n\n
         Stress is a normal part of life that can either help us learn and grow or can cause us significant problems.\n\n
Stress releases powerful neurochemicals and hormones that prepare us for action (to fight or flee).\n\n
	If we don\'t take action, the stress response can create or worsen health problems.\n\n
	Prolonged, uninterrupted, unexpected, and unmanageable stresses are the most damaging.\n\n
	Stress can be managed by seeking support from loved ones, regular exercise, meditation or other relaxation techniques, structured timeouts, and learning new coping strategies to create predictability in our lives.
 \n \n	Many behaviors that increase in times of stress and maladaptive ways of coping with stress- drugs, pain medicines, alcohol, smoking, and eating  actually worsen the stress and can make us more reactive (sensitive) to further stress.
 \n\n 	Risk factors for unmanageable stress include a lack of adequate social support.\n\n
	While there are promising treatments for stress, the management of stress is mostly dependent on the ability and willingness of a person to make the changes necessary for a healthy lifestyle.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="depr"> \n\n
        Depression is a state of low mood and aversion to activity. It can affect a person\'s thoughts, behavior, motivation, feelings,
        and sense of well-being. It may feature sadness, difficulty in thinking and concentration and a significant increase or
        decrease in appetite and time spent sleeping. People experiencing depression may have feelings of dejection, hopelessness
        and, sometimes, suicidal thoughts. It can either be short term or long term. The core symptom of depression is said to be
        anhedonia, which refers to loss of interest or a loss of feeling of pleasure in certain activities that usually bring joy to
        people. Depressed mood is a symptom of some mood disorders such as major depressive disorder
        or dysthymia; it is a normal temporary reaction to life events, such as the loss of a loved one; and it is also a symptom of
        some physical diseases and a side effect of some drugs and medical treatments.
        \n\n
    </string>
</resources>
